A Guide to the Purnell W. Choppin papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 1992:039 FA1073 FA1073
Rockefeller Archive Center
Purnell W. Choppin papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 1992:039
1944-1985
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University.
Choppin, Purnell W.
FA1073
34.8 Cubic Feet
Other Finding Aids note
For Series 1 through 3 of the Choppin papers see:
FA151 Purnell W. Choppin papers, Rockefeller University Faculty
Conditions Governing Access note
Collection is closed to scholarly research, pending further processing.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 450 C455-U
Arrangement
Arranged in 6 series by file type -
Series 3: Lab Notes and Notebooks. Series 4: Reprints. Series 5: Scientific Work. Series 6: Grant Files. Series 7: Committee Files. Series 8: General Files.
Biographical / Historical
Purnell W. Choppin (1929- ) an animal virologist, came to Rockefeller University and hospital in 1957 under a fellowship from the National Foundation. For twenty eight years Dr. Choppin's research was primarily concerned with the influenza and parainfluenza viruses. His papers consist of lab notebooks, reports, minutes of meetings, printed materials, lectures, memoranda and correspondence. In 1970 he was appointed professor and senior physician and served as vice president for academic program (1983).
Choppin was born on July 4, 1929 in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, and attended Louisiana State University where he received an M.D. degree from its School of Medicine in 1953.
Professor Choppin served in an advisory capacity to several scientific organizations; the NIAID's influenza Commision, Markey Scholars Program and as chairman of the Virology Study Section of the National Institute of Health.
In 1983 Dr. Choppin received the Howard Taylor Rickett Award of the University of Chicago. He also served as Chairman of the Virology Department at the Howard Hughes Institute in New York.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: correspondence and memoranda, notes and notebooks, meeting and committee records, Rockefeller University files, applications, grant information, article manuscripts and reprints.
Biology -- Research; Medical research; Viruses -- Research; Immunology; Immunology -- Research
- Reprints, 4
  - Reprints by Subject, 4_1
    - Bacteria and Phage, 1957-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Influenza IV, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Adenoviruses, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Antigen - Antibody (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Arboviruses (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Avian tumor Viruses (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Enteroviruses, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - Foot and Mouth Disease, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Fowl Plaque, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Infectious Mononucleosis, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Lysomes, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Microtubules, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Mumps, 1958-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Frog Tumor Viruses, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - GD VII - EMC, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - HHB-Guanidine, 1954-1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Herpesviruses, 1958-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
    - Influenza III, 1952-1964 (Box 1, Folder 21-22)
    - Plant Viruses (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Soluable Antigens (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Tissue Culture, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Cell - RNA (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Immune Reactions (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
    - Laboratory Rodents (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Visna and Slow Viruses, SSPE (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
    - Miscellaneous Viruses, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 33-35)
    - Viruses - General (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Inhibition of Multiplication, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
    - Measles, 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Reprints, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
    - Influenza (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - SV5 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Influenza - Kilborne (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
    - Influenza II (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Influenza, 1952-1968 (Box 2, Folder 15-17)
    - Poxviruses, 1956-1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Rabies, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Reoviruses, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Sendai, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Neurovirology, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Papova Virus, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Picornaviruses (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - PVM Reprints, 1944-1952 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Newcastle (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Tumor Viruses, 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Vaccinia Virus, 1961-1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Vascular Stomatitis Virus (VSV) (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Virus Structure (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
    - Myxovirus Receptor Interaction (Box 3, Folder 24-25)
    - Myxovirus and other reports (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Formation of Poliovirus (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Viral Study (Box 4, Folder 1-6)
  - Reprints by Others, 4_2
    - Champe, S. P. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Crowell, R. L. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Grayston, J. T. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Green, M. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Henle, W. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Bablanian, R. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Blough, H. A. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Bratt, M. A.; Robinson, W. S.; Duesberg, P. H. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Henson, J. B. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Howe, C. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Jenkins, H. M. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Kingsbury, D. W. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Loh, P. C. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Rapp, F. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Roizman, B. (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - Sinsheimer, R. L. (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
  - Reprints by Choppin, 4_3
    - Oligopeptides Inhibit Membrane Fusion Studies on Site Action (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Studies on Second Protein Enclosed by Neuraminidase Gene of Influenza B (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Oliogopeptides as Special Antiviral Agents (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Gene Structure and Replication of Influenza Virus (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
    - Sub Acute Sclerosing Paneencephalitis Studies Measle Virus (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Membrane Protein and Virus Virulence (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Human Virology Chapter (Box 4, Folder 14-18)
    - Spliced and Unspliced Messenger RNA (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Complete Nucleotide Sequence of Neuroaminidase Gene of Influenza (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Assembly of Sendai M Protein (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Enhancement of Membrane Fusing Activity of Sendai Virus (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Failure to Detect MV Protein in MS (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Studies on the Helical Nucleocapsid of Influenza (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Enhanced Yields of Measle Virus (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Influenza B Virus Genome Sequence and Stuctural Organization of RNA (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Sequence of RNA Segment 7 of Influenza B Virus Genome (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Relationship of Conformational Changes in Sendai Virus Nucleo (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Multiple Influenza mRNs - ICN ULCA (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Segment 7 mRNAs (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Identification of a Second Protein (M2) (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Conservation of Influenza Virus Membrane Protein (M2) Amino Acid (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Presentation at Meeting, Infectious Disease Society, New Orleans, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Influenza B Virus RNA Segment 8 Codes for Non-Stuctural Proteins (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Effect of Vandate on 10nm Filaments (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Inhibition of Neuraminidase by Hakide Ions (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Influenza B - New York Epidemic, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Mapping Two Overlapping Genes for Polypeptides Nsl and Ns2 on Segment 8 of the Influenza Virus Genome (PNAS) (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Structure and Variation in Influenza Virus, W. G. Laver (ed.) (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Conformation of Helical Nucleocapsids (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Sequence of Interuppted mRNAs, and Coned DNA (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Specific Inhibition of Paramyxovirus of Replication by Oligopeptide (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Immunological Studies of Paramyxovirus Glycoprotein (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Specific Inhibition of Paramyxovirus by Hydrophobic Olygopeptide (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - CIBA Symposium Manuscript (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Perspectives in Virology, 1980 February (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Journal Infectious Disease Editorial (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Measles Virus Proteins in Brain (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Synthesis of Sendai Virus Polypeptides in Infected Cells (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Protease Activation Mutants of Sendai Virus (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Sulfated Components of Enveloped Viruses (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Interactions of Paramyxovirus Glycoproteins with the Cell Surface (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Biological Role of Host-Dependent Proteolytic Cleavage (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Synthesis of Influenza Virus Proteins in Infected Cells (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Activation of Parainfluenza Viruses through Host-Dependent Cleavage (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Activation of Sendai Virus Fusion (F) Involves Change (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Hospital Practice Article - Influenza (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
    - Parainfluenza Viruses and their Interactions (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Isolation and Characterization of Ribonucleoprotein in Substructure from Rous Sarcoma Virus (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - A Specific Labeling Procedure for Proteins on the Outer Surface of Membranes (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Stucture and Assembly of Viral Membranes (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - The Structure of the Ribonucleoprotein of Influenza Virus (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Isolation of Paramyxovirus Glycoproteins Association of both Hem and Neuraminidase Activities with larger SV5 Glycoprotein (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Influenza Proteins II (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Isolation and Purification of the Envelope Proteins of NDV Virus (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Isolation and Properties of an RNA Polimerase from Influenza Virus (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Proteolytic Cleavage of the Hemmagglutinin Polypeptide of Influ Virus (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Structures Associated with the Polio Virus RNA Replication Complex (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Proteins of Viral Membranes (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Organization of Lipid Phase in Viral Membrane Effects on Variation (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Distinct Carbohydrate Components of Influenza Virus Glycoproteins (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Proteolytic Cleavage by Plasmin of the HA Polypeptide of Influenza (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Isolation of Paramyxovirus Glycoproteins (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Studies of Proteolytic Cleavage and Glycosylation of Influenza A and B (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Replication of Myxoviruses Comprehensive Virology (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Identification of Biological Activities of Paramyxovirus Glyco-proteins (Sendai Virus) (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Reproduction of Paramyxoviruses (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Interaction of the HN Protein of a Myxovirus with N. Acid (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Enhancement of Infectivity of Influenza (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - The Structure of Influenza Viruses (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Role of Viral Envelope Proteins in Pahtogenesis (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - New Influenza B Virus Glycoprotein (NB) (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Fusion of Sendai Virus with Lyposomes (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Biochemistry Annual Review of Influenza Viruses (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Annals of Neurology Editorial (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Annalogues of Viral Plypeptides (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Biochemical Studies on Cell Fusion II (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Biochemical Studies on Cell Fusion I (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Synthesis of Sendai Virus Polypeptides II Intracellular (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Synthesis of Polypeptides in Sendai Virus Infected Cells III (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Synthesis of Influenza Virus Polypeptides in Cells Resistant to a-aman (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Cambridge Landsberger (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Determination by Peptide Mapping in Sendai Virions (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Loss on Serial Passage of Rhesus Monkey Cells (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - SV5 and Sendai Lamb., Cambridge (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Influenza Polypeptides Lamb., Cambridge (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Paramyxovirus Glycoproteins - 77 Scheid, Cambridge (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Concepts in Viral Pathogenesis - Due April 1, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Analysis of Sendai Virus mRNAs with CDNA Clones of Viral Genes (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Studies on Synthesis Influenza B Virus NB Glycoprotein (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Tumogenicity of Cell Lines with Altered Lipid Composition (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - NB Glycoprotein of Influenza B Virus (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Measles Virus Polypeptide Synthesis in Infected Cells (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Analysis of Carbohydrates by Radio-Gas Chromatography (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Comprehensive Virology, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Evidence of Ninth Influenza Viral Polypeptide (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Influenza with Paramyxovirus Stimulates Synthesis of Polypeptide (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Reconstruction of Membranes with Individual Glycoproteins (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Cellular Proteases and Viral Pathogenecity A.C.C.A. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Measles and SSPE Virus Proteins (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Carbohydrate Structure of Glycoproteins (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Involvement of Microtubules and 10nm Filaments (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Role of Host Proteases in Interactions (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - A Ninth Unique Influenza Viral-Coded Polyptide (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Immunological Evidence Synthesis of Canine Distemper Virus Polypeptides (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Role of Paramyxovirus Glycoprotein's in (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Invitro Synthesis of Structural and Nonstructural Proteins (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Segment 8 of Influenza Virus Genome is Unique (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Abnormal antibodies in Measles Encephalitis (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Relationship between Movement of Centrioles in Syncytia (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Lack of Synthesis of M in Brain Cells in SSPE (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Membrane Fusing Activity of Paramyxovirus Envelope (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Polypeptides of Canine Distemper Virus (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Importance of Antibodies of Fusion Glycoprotein (F) (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Reviews of Infectious Diseases (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Role of Viral Glycoproteins in Virus Absorption (Box 6, Folder 26-27)
    - Morbiliviruses and Neurological Disease (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Comparison of Polypeptides of Four Measles Virus Strains (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Two Disulfide-linked Polypeptide Chains (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Polypeptide Synthesis in SV5-Infected Cells (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Lecithin Metabolism and Cell Fusion (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Immune Cytolysis and Cell Fusion (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Lipids of Plasma Membranes and SV5 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Chemical Composition of SV5 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Microtubules and Nuclear Movement, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Nucleic Acid of SV5 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - SV5 Replication - Super Infection with Polio (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - NDV - Length of Nucleocapsid (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - D. H. H. (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - The Parainfluenza virus SV5 and its Relationship to Cell Membrane, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - The Proteins of Parainfluenza Virus SV5 II Carbohydrate (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Influenza RNA, MDBK and Hela Cells (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Structure and Assembly of Influenza and Parainfluenza Viruses, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Phenetypic Myxing SV5 and VSV, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Glycosphingolipids of Plasma Membranes of Cultured Cells (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Plasma Membrane Lipids and Parainfluenza Virus Assembly, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - An EM Study of the Influenza Virus-Infected Cell, 1969 August (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Acrylamide Gels SV5 and Nucleocapsid (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Influenza Virus in MDBX Cells (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Visna Virus Proteins (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Helix of Paramyxovirus Nucleocapsid, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Structure of the Lipid Phase of Raucher Murine Leukemia Virus (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Influenza Virus Structural and Nonstructural Proteins in Infected Cells, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Proteins of Vesicular Stomatitis Virus (VSV) Phenotypically-nixed VSV-SV5 Virions, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Identification of the Spike Proteins of Rous Sarcoma Virus, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Viral Atlas, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Spin Label ESR Study of the Lipid Containing Membrane of Influenza Virus, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Parainfluenza Virus Surface Projections (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Glycolipid Content of VSV Grown in Baby Hamster Kidney Cells (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Proteins and Glycoproteins of Paramyxovirus - A Comparison of SV5 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - An EM Study of Presence or Absence of Neuraminic Acid in Enveloped Virus (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Membrane of Sindbis Virus - Location of the Glycoprotein (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Nucleocapsid Protein Subunits of SV5, New Castle Disease Virus and Sendai Virus, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Influenza Virus Protein I Analysis of Polypeptides of Virion (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Isolation and Charactererization on Nonglycosylated Membrane Protein, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Miles Symposium Structure of Influenza Virus MS, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Activation of Cell Fusion and Infectivity by Proteolytic Cleavage of Sendai Virus Glycoprotein, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Proteolytic Cleavage of Subunits of Nucleocapsid of SV5, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Reprints by Choppin, 1957, 1960-1985 (Box 7, Folder 20-27)
- Scientific Work, 5
  - Prints - Emergence Filament (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Flu - Ether, 1963 August 10 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Trypsin - Sugg Virus, 1961 March 22 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Flu and Trypsin PCMB Untreated, 1961 February 20 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Flu - Internal Component, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Ether - Formalin Experiment, 1961 April 10 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - A-Persian Gulf, 1952-1961 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Ether, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Trypsin - PCMB, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - NWS, MB Ether Passage, 1961 January 17 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Flu - Filaments Pleomorphism, 1961 February 17 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - E. M. Absorption and Penetration (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Second for Ether Paper (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - E. M. - Selected Flu-Ether (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - References - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Course, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Tissue Culture - Rfs Puck (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Parasitic Immunology, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Biochemical Methods Seminar, 1962 March 28 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Prints of E. M. III (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - E. M. - Life (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Budding Virus Flu and Paraflu, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Mumps (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Enterrovirus Inhibitor Serum (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Infectious Mononucleosis (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Horse Serum DEAE Cellulose (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Influenza Commission Armed Forces Epid. Board, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 54-55)
  - Slow Viruses (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Blood and Bone Marrow Cells - Wright's Stain (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - R1/5 Plus Filaments, Sphere, Passage, 1960 September 19 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Science Tools (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Strain Slips - R1, 1957 January 6 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - West Nile Virus (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Influenza B Virus RNA Segment 8 Codes (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
  - N-C Paper (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Data I, II, III, 1960 June 27 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
  - Heterogeneity of Coxsackie B4 Virus (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Influenza Filaments - Surface, 1961 January 31 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Plaque Formation by Influenza A2 Virus in Monkey Kidney Cells (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Multiple Schlerosis (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
  - Inactivation of Enterovirus Infection by S. R. P. C. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Inactivation of Enterovirus Infection by Bal (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Multiplication of Two Kinds of Influenza A2 Virus (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Rough Mss - Filaments (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Trypsin-Flu, Nasa Receptors (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - CIBA Symposium, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Interactions of Ether Disrupted Influenza A2 Virus (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - The Morphology of SV5 Virus (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Multiplication of a Myxovirus (SV5) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Poliovirus ADS to CNS (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - SV5 - Actinomycin D (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Collected Tables - sliced-made (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Data-Flu M. K. (Box 8, Folder 26-27)
  - E. M. Study SV5 - Cell Interactions (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Cell Fusing Activity of Visna Virus (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Visna Plaque Assay (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Immunology Chapter (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Cell Membrane Roll SV5 - MK vs BHK (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - AAAF (Box 8, Folder 33-34)
  - Emergence of Influenza Virus Filaments from Host Cells (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Florida Symposium, 1966 December (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - SV5 Nucelocapsid Isolation and Properties (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - PVM I - Replication and Properties (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - PVM II - Structure and Morphogenesis (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Biological Properties of VSV Glycoprotein I (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - II Effects of the Host Cell on Hemagglutination (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Circular Paramyxovirus Nucleocapsids (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - The Transcriptase Complex of Paramyxovirus SV5 (Box 8, Folder 43-44)
  - Old Department Reprints, 1946-1952 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Old Department Reprints, 1954-1956 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Myxovirus Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Myxovirus General (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - I, II and III Manuscripts (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Data - SH II (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hart Gels (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Peptide Map Gels (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Protein Gels (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Nuclease Mapping Gels (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - RNA Gels (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Capping (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - DRB (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Cloning Gels (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Choppin, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Extras - Frontispiece (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - E. M. - SV5 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - SV5 Extras (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Sendai (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - SV5 Originals for Paper (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Mumps and NDV Experiment, 1963 August 27 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - W3 - SV5 Selected (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - SV5 Seconds (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - SV5 Seconds II (Box 9, Folder 23-24)
  - LKB Pump (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Amicon 8MC (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Charts (Box 29)
  - Graphs (Box 29)
  - Photographs (Box 29)
- Grant Files, 6
  - Training Grant - Correspondence Discussions - Award Sheets (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - Pre and Postdoctoral Three Year Limits on NRSA (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Training Grant Renewal - 10 Year, 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Virology Training Grant, 1981-1986 (Box 9, Folder 30-32)
  - Appointments - Training Grant (Box 9, Folder 33-34)
  - Training Grant - 02 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Training Grant - 03 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Training Grant - 03 Appts. (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Training Grant - 04 Appts. (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Training Grant - 04, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Training Grant - 05, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Training Grant - 05 Appts., 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Program Project Grant 1975 - Project 06 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Program Project Grant 1975 - Project 07 and 08 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Program Project Grant 1975 - Computer Graphic Request (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Program Project Grant 1975 - Project 09 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Program Project Grant 1975 - C. D. Grant Request and Project 10 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - MD - Ph.D. Training Grant (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Old Data (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Silverstein, 1972, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - NSF Renewal, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - MS Grant Application, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
  - NIH AI - 05600 01-08, 1963-1971 (Box 10, Folder 15)